Class of 1893 Records, 1886-1967, 1983, 1990, 1993-95
Smith College Archives
Class of 1893 Records
1886-1967, 1983, 1990, 1993-95
Smith College. Class of 1893.
RG 80 UUID:dc9174cc-5566-4aa0-acfe-352f798a03bb
11 boxes (4.6 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, photo albums, correspondence, letters, scrapbooks, class notes, newspaper clippings, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1893.
Historical Note
The Class of 1893 was the fifteenth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1893 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1893. Types of materials include black and white photographs, photo albums, correspondence, letters, scrapbooks, class notes, newspaper clippings, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1893.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1893 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1893: Collation 1893 (Box 1472, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Commencement 1893 (Box 1472, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Commencement Music 1893 (Box 1472, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Commencement Photographs 1893 (Box 1472, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Groups 1889-93 (Box 1472, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Groups 1889-91, other n.d. (Box 1472, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: History N.d. (Box 1472, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Ivy Day 1893 (Box 1472, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Ivy Day Photographs 1893 (Box 1472, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Junior Prom 1892 (Box 1472, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Class Letters 1910, 1912, 1914-19, 1922-33 (Box 1472, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Fund Letters 1930, 1936 (Box 1472, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Lists 1928-29, 1931, 1933-34, other n.d. (Box 1472, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Monogram and Stationery 1893 (Box 1473, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-General and Undated 1893-94, 1908, 1910, 1913-14, 1918, 1921-23, 1925, 1927-28, 1933, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1473, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-3rd 1896 (Box 1473, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-5th 1898 (Box 1473, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-10th 1903 (Box 1473, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-15th 1908 (Box 1473, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-17th 1910 (Box 1473, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-20th 1913 (Box 1473, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-25th 1918 (Box 1473, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-30th 1923 (Box 1473, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-35th 1928 (Box 1473, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-40th 1933 (Box 1473, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-45th 1938 (Box 1473, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-50th 1943 (Box 1473, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Reunions-55th 1948 (Box 1473, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Senior Dramatics 1893 (Box 1473, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Songs N.d. (Box 1473, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: Sophomore Reception 1889 (Box 1473, Folder 18)
- Class of 1893: Sophomore-Senior Reception for 1891 1891 (Box 1473, Folder 19)
- Class of 1893: Class Supper 1903, other n.d. (Box 1473, Folder 20)
- Class of 1893: Adams, Ella Maria 1924, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Adams, Martha Rumery 1928, 1939, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Andrus, Jessie Fish 1928, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Ayer, Frances May (Photographs, etc) 1925, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Baker, C(aroline) Isabel (Photographs, etc) 1893, 1935, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Ball, Mina 1890, 1923, 1928, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Barrows, Harriet Louise 1924, 1928, 1930, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Bigelow, Harriet Williams (Box 1474, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Blackstone, Martha Blackwell 1910, 1916-17 (Box 1474, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Blackstone, Martha Blackwell (Photographs, etc) 1893, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Bourland, Caroline Brown (Box 1474, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Boynton, Bertha Ella (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Bradbury, Ellen Brooks 1889, 1924, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Bradbury, Ellen Brooks (Photographs) 1893 (Box 1474, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Bradford, Stella Stevens 1918, 1922-23, 1927-28, 1930, 1936, 1950, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Bradford, Stella Stevens (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Bragaw, Mary N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: Brewster, Anna Gertrude 1898-99, 1903-04, 1967, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 18)
- Class of 1893: Buckingham, Grace Hammersley (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 19)
- Class of 1893: Burgess, Mary Ellen (Photographs, etc) 1894, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 20)
- Class of 1893: Busbey, Winifred Grace (Photographs, etc) 1929, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 21)
- Class of 1893: Calhoun, Flora Jane (Photographs, etc) 1928, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 22)
- Class of 1893: Campbell, Jennie Isabel 1924, 1928, 1933, 1935-36, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 23)
- Class of 1893: Carson, Ethel Daggett 1893, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 24)
- Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey 1924, 1928, 1938 (Box 1474, Folder 25)
- Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey (Photographs) 1892-93 (Box 1474, Folder 26)
- Class of 1893: Choate, Mary Lillian 1963 (Box 1474, Folder 27)
- Class of 1893: Clark, Abigail Williams 1927, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 28)
- Class of 1893: Cook, Anna Emeline 1918 (Box 1474, Folder 29)
- Class of 1893: Cook, Ellen Parmelee (Box 1474, Folder 30)
- Class of 1893: Cook, Mary A. 1928, 1932, 1935-36, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 31)
- Class of 1893: Cooper, Caroline Ella N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 32)
- Class of 1893: Copeland, Mary Emma (Photographs) 1933, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 33)
- Class of 1893: Corliss Lamont, Florence 1938, 1940, 1983, 1995 (Box 1474, Folder 34)
- Class of 1893: Corser, Theressa Isabel 1938, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 35)
- Class of 1893: Crittenden, Daisy 1890 (Box 1474, Folder 36)
- Class of 1893: Cross, Jane P. 1933, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 37)
- Class of 1893: Darling, Frances 1928, 1933, 1936, 1942 (Box 1474, Folder 38)
- Class of 1893: Davis, Ina Forrest 1928, 1939, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 39)
- Class of 1893: Denman, M(artha) Luella (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 40)
- Class of 1893: Dole, Mary Mitchell (Photographs) 1889-90, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 41)
- Class of 1893: Dorr, Cora Louise (Photographs) 1891, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 42)
- Class of 1893: Dow, Marion Durant (Photographs) 1928, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 43)
- Class of 1893: Du Bois, Mary Susan (Photographs) 1928, 1933, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 44)
- Class of 1893: Duncan, Mabel Ticknor (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1474, Folder 45)
- Class of 1893: Dwight, Julia Strong Lyman (Photographs) 1924 (Box 1474, Folder 46)
- Class of 1893: Dyer, Josephine Tyler 1924, other n.d. (Box 1474, Folder 47)
- Class of 1893: Eaton, Mary Field 1936 (Box 1475, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Emerson, Maud Lenore 1918, 1921, 1923, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Entwistle, Antoinette (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1475, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Estes, Jean Louise (Photographs) 1928, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Evans, Alice R. N.d. (Box 1475, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Fales, Katharine Mildred 1938 (Box 1475, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Farr, Flora Anna 1925, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Fay, Mary Caroline (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1475, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Field, Elizabeth Peck 1893, 1923 (Box 1475, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Field, Grace Bowers 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Flagg, Gertrude E. 1936, 1952, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Flagg, Gertrude E. (Notebook) 1900-01 (Box 1475, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Frisbee, Julia Catharine 1928, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Fuller, Violet (Photographs, etc) 1886-87, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Gamwell, Olive Wells 1928, 1932-33, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Grant, Janet Clara (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1475, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour 1890, 1893, 1927-28, 1933, 1960, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Class Notes) 1892-93 (Box 1475, Folder 18)
- Class of 1893: Hagar, Mary Lyon (Photographs, etc) 1891-93, 1925, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 19)
- Class of 1893: Hamilton, Mary Emma 1893, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 20)
- Class of 1893: Hardy, Grace Maud (Photographs, etc) 1928, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 21)
- Class of 1893: Hartwell, Maud Appleton (Photographs, etc) 1889, 1904, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 22)
- Class of 1893: Harwood, Mary Emma (Photographs, etc) 1893, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 23)
- Class of 1893: Holden, Harriet Eleanor (Photographs, etc) 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 24)
- Class of 1893: Howe, Jennie 1925, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 25)
- Class of 1893: Hudson, Harriet Louise (Photographs, etc) 1928, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 26)
- Class of 1893: Jackson, Florence 1892, 1903, 1925, 1928, 1933, 1936-38 (Box 1475, Folder 27)
- Class of 1893: Jackson, Florence (Alumnae Material) 1910, 1913, 1916, 1918-28, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 28)
- Class of 1893: Jeffrey, Florence 1893, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 29)
- Class of 1893: Johnson, Anna Louise (Photographs, etc) 1893, 1928, other n.d. (Box 1475, Folder 30)
- Class of 1893: Kelly, Susan Maria 1924, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Kidder, Anna Laura (Special Student 1884-1893) 1909 (Box 1476, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Knox, Susan Varick (Correspondence) 1889-1891 (Box 1476, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Knox, Susan Varick (Correspondence) 1892-1893 (Box 1476, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Knox, Susan Varick (Photographs, etc) 1927, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Lamson, Marion Helena (Photographs, etc) 1924, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Landon, Grace 1920, 1923-24, 1928-29, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Landon, Grace (Photographs) 1891, 1893, 1919-21, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Landon, Mary (Photographs, etc) 1890-91, 1893, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Lane, Grace 1893, 1939, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Leggett, Blanche Chipman 1927, 1930 (Box 1476, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Leggett, Blanche Chipman (Photographs, etc) 1893, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Lentell, Mary Althea 1925, 1928, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Lewis, Margaret (Photographs, etc) 1893, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Libby, Blanche Edith (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1476, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Love, Grace Mabel (Photographs) 1890, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Lyman, Virginia Dummer (Photographs, etc) 1924-25, 1928, 1933 (Box 1476, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: May, Margarita Britton (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1476, Folder 18)
- Class of 1893: McConway, Anne 1892, 1918, 1923-24, 1926, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 19)
- Class of 1893: Meisel, Clara Eveline 1886, 1891, 1925, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 20)
- Class of 1893: Mills, Harriet Chidsey (Photographs, etc) 1928, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 21)
- Class of 1893: Morris, Anne Louise (Photographs, etc) 1890, 1928, 1936, 1950, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 22)
- Class of 1893: Morse, Lillian Kimball 1924 (Box 1476, Folder 23)
- Class of 1893: Murkland, Charlotte Marie (Photographs, etc) 1910, 1928, 1993-94, other n.d. (Box 1476, Folder 24)
- Class of 1893: Newell, Margaret Farrington 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Newton, M(ary) Elizabeth (Photographs, etc) 1891, 1893, 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Norris, Charlotte (Photographs, etc) 1928, 1935-36, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Oakes, Margaret Maude 1937 (Box 1477, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Parker, Grace Bursley (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Pearson, Ellen Gertrude 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Perkins, Adelaide French 1937, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Poole, Harriet Schoedde (Photographs, etc) 1893, 1897, 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Port, Irma Genette 1924, 1928, 1933, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Pratt, Edith Louise (Photographs) 1894, 1899, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Pratt, Laura Melancia (Photographs, etc) 1893, 1930, 1935, 1937 (Box 1477, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Prentiss, Mary Ellen 1933, 1936, 1954 (Box 1477, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Presbrey, Laura Edith 1891, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Procter, Adeline Winthrop (Photographs, etc) 1928, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Putnam, Helen Langley (Photographs, etc) 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Randall, Bertha Thatcher (Photographs, etc) 1928, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Rich, Alice Elizabeth 1914, 1923, 1928, 1931, 1933 (Box 1477, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: Richardson, Edith Maria 1892, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 18)
- Class of 1893: Richardson, Mary Lincoln (Photographs, etc) 1936, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 19)
- Class of 1893: Rumsey, Olive 1910, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 20)
- Class of 1893: Sabin, Florence Rena 1892, 1904, 1909, 1916, 1918, 1921, 1923-26, 1929, 1931-41, 1943, 1945-46, 1960-61, 1990 (Box 1477, Folder 21)
- Class of 1893: Sanford, Mabel Warren (Photographs, etc) 1895-96, 1903, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 22)
- Class of 1893: Scovill, Florence May 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 23)
- Class of 1893: Shepard, Bertha Maria 1920, 1923, 1926, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 24)
- Class of 1893: Shepard, Clara Alida (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 25)
- Class of 1893: Sherrill, Cecilia Adelaide (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 26)
- Class of 1893: Shoemaker, Mary Erety (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 27)
- Class of 1893: Short, Mabel Amanda (Photographs) 1893 (Box 1477, Folder 28)
- Class of 1893: Sigsbee, Anna Lockwood 1898, 1928, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 29)
- Class of 1893: Smith, Bertha Chester 1890, 1923, n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 30)
- Class of 1893: Smith, Caroline Frances 1928 (Box 1477, Folder 31)
- Class of 1893: Smith, Elisabeth 1931, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 32)
- Class of 1893: Smith, Florence Virginia (Photographs) 1893, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 33)
- Class of 1893: Smith, Frances Grace (Box 1477, Folder 34)
- Class of 1893: Soule, Elizabeth Nye (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 35)
- Class of 1893: Sparks, Mary Estelle (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 36)
- Class of 1893: Steele, Grace Maria 1928 (Box 1477, Folder 37)
- Class of 1893: Stevens, Grace Mildred (Photographs, etc) 1890-91, 1893, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 38)
- Class of 1893: Stone, Charlotte Sackett (Box 1477, Folder 39)
- Class of 1893: Stone, Myra Josephine (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 40)
- Class of 1893: Stratton, Lena Sophia 1938 (Box 1477, Folder 41)
- Class of 1893: Strong, Gertrude Helen (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1477, Folder 42)
- Class of 1893: Strong, Julia Worthington 1938, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 43)
- Class of 1893: Strong, Maud Evelyn 1939, other n.d. (Box 1477, Folder 44)
- Class of 1893: Taft, Edith Lockwood (Photographs, etc) 1938, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Tapley, Elizabeth Pierce 1924, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Thompson, Bertha Mary (Photographs) 1893, 1906, 1928, 1931, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Torr, Grace T. 1928, 1933, 1935, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Twining, Edith de Gueldry (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1478, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Twitchell, Gertrude Marble (Photographs) 1893, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Vanderbeek, Mary Courtland (Blueprint Album, etc) 1892, 1924, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Ward, Grace 1924, 1928, 1933, 1936, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Ward, Lily Emily (Photographs) (Box 1478, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Waring, Mary Kimberley 1894, 1900, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Watterson, Helen Mary 1928, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Watterson, Roberta Franc 1931, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Weeks, Imogene 1923, 1931, 1933, 1936, 1938, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Wheeler, Frances (Photographs, etc) 1923, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Whitman, Helen Hobart 1895, 1937, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Wilcox, Elizabeth Kenyon (Photographs) 1890, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Williams, Bessie Hastings (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1478, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: Williston, Agnes Louise 1893, 1928, 1933, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 18)
- Class of 1893: Williston, Elizabeth (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1478, Folder 19)
- Class of 1893: Wilson, Frances N.d. (Box 1478, Folder 20)
- Class of 1893: Woolen, Maria 1893, 1928, 1933, 1967, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 21)
- Class of 1893: Wyatt, Mabel Preston 1893, 1928, 1937-38, other n.d. (Box 1478, Folder 22)
- Class of 1893: Young, Emma Estelle N.d. (Box 1478, Folder 23)
- Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey (Scrapbook, Photo Album) Various dates (Box 1479)
- Class of 1893: Carter, Edith Hovey (Scrapbook, Photo Album) Various dates (Box 1479.1)
- Class of 1893: Field, Grace Bowers (Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1480)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Index) 1889-1893 (Box 1481, Folder 1)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Dec 1889) 1889 (Box 1481, Folder 2)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Jun 1890) 1890 (Box 1481, Folder 3)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1890) 1890 (Box 1481, Folder 4)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Nov-Dec 1890) 1890 (Box 1481, Folder 5)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Feb 1891) 1891 (Box 1481, Folder 6)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Mar-Apr 1891) 1891 (Box 1481, Folder 7)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-May-Jun 1891) 1891 (Box 1481, Folder 8)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1891) 1891 (Box 1481, Folder 9)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Nov-Dec 1891) 1891 (Box 1481, Folder 10)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Feb 1892) 1892 (Box 1481, Folder 11)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Mar-Apr 1892) 1892 (Box 1481, Folder 12)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-May-Jun 1892) 1892 (Box 1481, Folder 13)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1892) 1892 (Box 1481, Folder 14)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Nov-Dec 1892) 1892 (Box 1481, Folder 15)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Jan-Feb 1893) 1893 (Box 1481, Folder 16)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-Mar-Apr 1893) 1893 (Box 1481, Folder 17)
- Class of 1893: Greene, Mary Seymour (Correspondence-May-Jun 1893) 1893 (Box 1481, Folder 18)